LORRAINE BAYNOSA, RN, MSN

Birthplace: Los Angeles, California, U.S.

Language: English
Citizenship United States

Current Work Address: 11301 Wilshire Blvd, Bldg 500, Los Angeles, CA 90073

Personal E-mail Address <u>lorraine.baynosa@gmail.com</u>

Personal cell-phone (818) 390-4187

PROFILE Operating Room Nurse for nearly 19 years and current full-stack web developer student at UCLA

Extension Coding Bootcamp with intention to use coding skills to develop applications to reduce healthcare costs, enhance efficiency of healthcare processes, improve the interoperability of the

electronic health record, and reduce the disparity in delivery of quality care.

EXPERIENCE

2004-2005

2000-2000 Intensive Care Unit Nurse, Cardiothoracic Unit, UCLA Medical Center
2000/11-2006/09 Staff Nurse, Operating Room, VA Greater Los Angeles Healthcare System (GLA),
West LA Medical Center

• Experience in circulating and scrubbing for general, urology, plastic, orthopaedic/hand, ophthalmology, plastic, podiatry, gynecology, head and neck, vascular, thoracic, and cardiac surgery

Expertise in scrubbing and circulating for neurosurgery and cardiac surgery
 Laparoscopic Service Team Leader, Operating Room, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2006/10-2007/10 Risk Management, Nursing Service, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center 2006/10-2007/10 MRSA Project Coordinator, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2007/10-2010/07 Nurse Manager, Sterile Processing Services, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2007/06-2015/03 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Per Diem, Saint John's Health Center, Santa

Monica, CA

2014/12-2017/03 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Per Diem, UCLA, Santa Monica Medical Center,

Santa Monica, CA

2010/07-2017/03 Reusable Medical Equipment (RME) Coordinator, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center Consultant to Reusable Medical Equipment (RME) Program, VA GLA, West LA Medical

Center

2017/03-2018/04 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Kaiser Permanente Santa Clara Medical Center

EDUCATION

1995-1997	University of California, Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA
1997-1998	Los Angeles City College Los Angeles CA

1997-1998 Los Angeles City College, Los Angeles, CA

1998-2000 B.S. University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA in Nursing
 2004-2006 M.S. University of California, Los Angeles, CA in Nursing Administration

SKILLS

HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, Materialize), JQuery, Javascript, Firebase Realtime Database, Ajax calls, Google Maps API, NodeJS, MySQL, Express, Handlebars, Sequelize

LANGUAGES

HTML, Javascript

REFERENCES

Available on request